Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1930s-1992
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 2: Academic Career/Government Appointments, 1930s-1992
  - Issues: Energy, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Issues: The environment, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Issues: Food and agriculture, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Issues: Foreign policy, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Issues: General, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Issues: Government reform, July 15, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Gun control issue area, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Issues: Hatch Act, February 1980 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Issues: Health, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Issues: Housing, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Issues: Impeachment, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Issues: Inflation, 1974-1981 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Issues: Land use, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Moral majority, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Productivity memo to JLF from Chuck, June 29, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Issues: Regional issues, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Issues: R + D, October 1-3, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Issues: Senior citizens, 1973-1980 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Social security, federal employees, newspaper clippings, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Issues: Transportation, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Issues: Veterans, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Issues 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Issue papers, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Issue papers, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Issue papers, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Issue papers, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of human resources, expenses, 1981-1984 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of human resources, newspaper clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Labor and human resource issues in Virginia, 1970s-1980s (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Virginia's investment in job training: A proposal for Governor's economic development projects, August 29, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Changing health care cost, December 1985 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Prevention in human resources, December 1985 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Human resources agencies in Virginia, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Speeches on human resources, 1983-1985 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - New directions for human resources, January 10, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to Stuart Connock from JLF, January 8, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Migrant farm workers on Virginia's eastern shore, January 10, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Baliles, May and September 1986 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Aging program, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - American culture seminar, April 1987 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - American Forestry Association, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - George Mason University campus development team, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Caunox, Peter J., December 1990 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Center for conflict analysis and resolution, 1988-1991 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Conflict resolution course John Burton material, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Dion, Jeffrey, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Dissertation committees, 1987-1991 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - General assembly, 1989-1991 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - George Mason University, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - George Mason University press, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - George Mason University, 1986-1991 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Government and legislative relations proposal, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Center for health policy at George Mason University, October 11, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Human services conference, 1986-1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Human services I & R council, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - International Hospice Institute, 1989-1991 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - George Mason University international institute, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Internationalizing the curriculum at George Mason University: A preliminary report, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - George Mason University job descriptions, administration and coordinators, 1987-1988 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - George Mason University, correspondence with President Johnson, 1987-1989 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - George Mason University, Lambda Alpha International, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Local government forum, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - George Mason University Democratic Club, April 1, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Northern Virginia chair in local government, 1989-1991 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Northern Virginia Institute, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Northern Virginia mediation service, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - The politics of economics and vice versa (or how economics and politicians frustrate each other), September 1987 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Report on the feasibility study for a Prince William center for higher education, April 1987 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - A proposal for a university presence in Prince William County, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Public affairs department, George Mason University, 1988-1991 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Public Choice Center, George Mason University, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Public Policy program search activities, George Mason University, 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Public Policy, George Mason University, 1987-1990 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Public Policy, George Mason University, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Institute of Public Policy, George Mason University, 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Public Policy, George Mason University, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Center for study of race and ethnic relations, George Mason University, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Reorganization, University Commission of 1983, George Mason University, 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Scheiber, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Southport Institute, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Southport Institute, 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Virginia alliance for the public service, George Mason University, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Outlines and reading lists for policy courses, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Government 401 public policy process, Spring 1991 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Government 463 lobbying and public policy, 1990? (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - George Mason University course, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Human resources policy seminar, Fall 1985 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Honor seminar Government 490, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Government 490 human and natural resources policy, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Government 490 seminar human and natural resources policy, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - PUAD 463 lobbying, Spring 1991 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Fisher PUAD 640, Spring 1986 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Policy course, Spring 1986 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - PUAD 640, Fall 1986 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - PUAD public policy process, Spring 1987 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - PUAD public policy process 640, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - PUAD 640, Fall 1988 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - PUAD 640, Spring 1989 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - PUAD 640, Fall 1989 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - PUAD 640, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - PUAD 640, Fall 1990 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - PUAD 640, Fall 1990 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - PUAD 749 issues in public policy, Spring 1990 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - PUAD 749 issues in public policy, Spring 1990 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Another look at the Metro campus and the Arlington community, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1988-1989 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Arlington George Mason University committee, 1980s (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Arlington George Mason University project, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Arlington George Mason University development committee, 1988-1990 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Arlington George Mason University development committee, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Arlington George Mason University report, I of III, 1989-1991 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Arlington George Mason University report, II of III, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Arlington George Mason University report, III of III, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Arlington George Mason University finance subcommittee, 1989-1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Arlington George Mason University program planning committee, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Arlington George Mason University program planning committee, December 1988 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - The new George Mason University Arlington campus: a program for an educating committee, December 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper clippings on George Mason University Arlington campus; Virginia Tech packet, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Arlington George Mason University campus, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Friends of George Mason University, Arlington campus, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University seminar, Fall 1985 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University PAD 691, Spring 1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Class - Political and economic perspectives on national policy, Spring 1984 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Directions for America, 1980s (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Directions for America, 1980s (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Abortion material, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Airports, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Assessment, newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Background material, debates, speeches, issues papers, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Beyer for Lieutenant Governor, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Bills cosponsored, September 16, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Bowdoin College, 1979-1980 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Campaign contributions, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Campaign, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Cards to JLF, 1988-1990 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation Lauds committee, 1988-1990 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Chesapeake future project, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - China trip, 1979-1980 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Claremont school of theology, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Coal, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Committee for national security, 1989-1990 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Common cause, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, 1988; 1990 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Congress, 1984-1991 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Finances, reporting and disclosure, 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Congressional financial disclosure, 1975-1980 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Conservation foundation, 1968-1989 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, political, April 14, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Democratic committee Arlington, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Democratic study group, August 21, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Duke paper, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Education, aging paper, 1988-1991 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Emerson, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Energy and environment, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Environment, July 1, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Environmental and energy study institute, 1988-1990 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Environmental study conference, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Environmental study conference, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Fairfax cultural task force, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Finances, 1974-1980 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Finances, budget, 1974-1980 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - JLF political, 1975-1979 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Former members of Congress, 1980-1990 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Foundations, 1986-1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Franking commission, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Proposed changes to the Hatch Act, February 23, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - House democrats, 93rd Congress, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Income security, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - International Hospice Institute (IHI), 1991 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Institute of energy analysis, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Lechner, Ira, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Loudoun, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Miller campaign, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Milliken campaign, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Fisher and Munsey press releases; Newspaper clippings on bilingual education, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous items: JLF articles and notes, 1960-1982 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Mitre lecture, November 10, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Mitre lecture, November 10, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Mitre lecture, November 10, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), Beyond distrust: Building bridges between congress and the executive, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), Congress and the executive: Improving the management and implementation of public policy, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), Presidential search committee, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Public Administration (NAPA), 1989-1991 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - National economists club, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Northern Virginia community foundation, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Papers, 1987-1991 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Papers, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Planned community archives at George Mason University, 1990-1991 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Political action organization, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Political campaigns (Van Huyck and Miller), 1991 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Polling, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Population reference bureau (PRB), 1991 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, ratings, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Quotations, miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Regulation, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Report on wood stoves, environmental consequences, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Resources for the future, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Resumes, 1987-1991 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Robb campaign, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Robb book, 1980s (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Robb book, 1983-1987 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Robb book, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Robb lectures, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Robb lectures, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Senate campaign, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Speeches I of II, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Speeches II of II, 1983-1988 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Statewide human services information and referral advisory council, Virginia, 1989-1991 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Tennis partners memo, 1970s (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Virginia environmental law journal, 1989-1991 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Weinberg campaign, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Paul Simon campaign, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - The wilderness society, 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - The wilderness society, 1987-1991 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - The wilderness society, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Frank Wolf, 1971-1978 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Wolf, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - World future society, 1988-1991 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - World resources institute, January 18, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Church programs, 1960s-1990s (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Fisher sermons I (church programs), 1970s-1980s (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Fisher sermons II (church programs), 1970s-1980s (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Talks and drafts of sermons, 1970s (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - JLF personal: Aeronautics and space engineering board, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - JLF personal: American forestry association, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - JLF personal: Aspen Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - JLF personal: Bowdoin College, 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - JLF personal: Commission on international relations, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - JLF personal: Commission on natural resources (National Research Council), 1981 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - JLF personal: Committee on Dulles and National airports, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - JLF personal: Former members of Congress, October 28, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - JLF personal: Miscellaneous business correspondence, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - JLF personal: Miscellaneous social correspondence, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - JLF personal: Cosmos club, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - JLF personal: Electrical power research institute (EPRI), 1981 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Institute for energy analysis, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - JLF letterhead, 1970s-1980s (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Peggy Fisher, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - JLF personal: George Mason University, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - JLF personal: George Washington University, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - JLF personal: Government affairs institute, OPM, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - JLF personal: Greater Washington research center, 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - JLF personal: Greater Washington research center, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - JLF personal: Help the aged, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - JLF personal: House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - JLF personal: Human environment center, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - JLF personal: Mitre, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Names and addresses, 1970s-1980s (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - JLF personal: National kidney foundation, June 9, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - JLF personal: Oberlin College, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Personal, 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Personal miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - JLF personal: Population reference bureau, 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - JLF personal: Resources for the future, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - JLF personal: Robb campaign, energy working group, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - JLF personal: Society for international development, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - JLF personal: 10th district, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - JLF personal: Unitarian universalist association, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Unitarian universalist association, 1965-1978 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - JLF personal: WMATA, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1986-1990 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Dissertation for Harvard University: Alaska: The development of our arctic frontier (part I) by Fisher, April 1, 1947 (Box 94)
  - Dissertation for Harvard University: Alaska: The development of our arctic frontier (part II) by Fisher, April 1, 1947 (Box 94)
  - Problems in the study of economic growth: Research in regional economic growth by Edgar M. Hoover and Fisher, July 1949 (Box 94)
  - Thesis for George Washington University by Fisher: Resources conservation in the University social science curriculum, November 12, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Concepts in regional economic development by Fisher, March 1958 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Implications of the new development in energy for the American economy, August 3-22, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - The adequacy of resources for economic growth in the United States by Fisher and Edward Boorstein, December 16, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Conservation for more and more people by Fisher, August 1960 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Our resource situation: Public policy and individual responsibility, August 1960 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - National Parks magazine: Framework for wilderness by Fisher, November 1960 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Public Administration Review: Resource policies and administration for the future by Fisher, Spring 1961 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - First World Conference on National Parks: Planning for a nation's system of parks by Marion Clawson and Fisher, June 30 - July 7, 1962 (Box 93, File 15)
  - Mid-century conference on resources for the future, conference program, December 2-4, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Natural resources projections and their contribution to technological planning by Fisher and Hans H. Landsberg, January 1962 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - The multiple use of our natural resources by Fisher, April 1962 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Resources in America's future by Hans H. Landsberg, Leonard L. Fischman, and Fisher, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Natural resources: Trends, policies and administration edited by Fisher, August 1963 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Profiles of the future: Resource projections by Fisher and Hans H. Landsberg, Summer 1963 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - World prospects for natural resources by Fisher and Neal Potter, 1964; 1972 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Natural Resources: Notes on resources education by Fisher, February 27 - March 1, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Resource policies for a great society, November 1964 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Interim report of the oil shale advisory board, February 1965 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - America 1980: Resources in 1980 by Fisher and Hans H. Landsberg, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - The relationship of material resources and population to economic and social development, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Man and Metro: Reflections on some problems of the national capital region, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Coping with crises in the natural resources, November 22, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Reflections on the formulation of regional policy by Fisher, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - The Register-Leader: Our greatest gamble by Fisher, November 1966 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Natural resource trends and their implications for the Rocky Mountain region by Fisher, October 1966 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Perspectives in Defense Management: Natural resources and the future of man by Fisher, November 1967 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - The job of the congressman, two signed books, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - The economic impact of TVA: Natural resource problems and TVA by Fisher, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Perspectives on natural resources and human resources by Fisher, January 1967 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - The Science Teacher: The public concern for conservation by Fisher, April 1967 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Environmental quality and urban living, April 4, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - The natural environment by Fisher in The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, May 1967 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Everyone's war by Fisher in The Register-Leader of the Unitarian Universalist Association, May 1967 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Limits on the exploitation of natural resources by Fisher in Technology Review, May 1968 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Energy needs: Expanding our resources by Fisher in The General Electric Forum, Summer 1968 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - New perspectives on conservation by Fisher, March 1969 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Economic and social aspects of environmental enhancement by Fisher in Man and His Environment, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Sound resource decisions: What kind of foresters will be needed? by Fisher in Journal of Forestry, August 1969 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Effects of population growth on natural resources and the environment, 91st Congress, September 15-16, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Environment comes in regional packages by Fisher in Regional Review Quarterly, April 1970 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - A larger future for soil conservation by Fisher in Turning Points in Time conference proceedings, August 9-12, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - An expanding future for soil conservation by Fisher in Journal of Soil and Water Conservation, November - December 1970 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Dimensions of the environmental crisis by Fisher in Zygon: Journal of Religion and Science, December 1970 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Environmental pollution and the future of man's earth by Fisher in Social Education, January 1971 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Policies for balanced growth by Fisher in Growth and Change: A Journal of Regional Development, April 1971 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Impact of population on resources and the environment by Fisher in The American Economic Review, May 1971 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Conservation as research, policy and action by Fisher, October 1971 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Resources for business by Fisher, February 7-9, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 2)